{
    "id": "fdb2d803c4ef49eeb607452a1ee12ee4",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He does not smoke, …………………………. does he drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize, ………………………. you will be punished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He must be asleep, ………………………….. there is no light in his room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been working hard, ………………………… he will pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We will promote him …………………………… he is efficient.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t help you, ………………………… you tell me the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks ……………………………. it might rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "if",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. she is poor, she is always neatly dressed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have such regard for him ……………………………… I will do anything to please him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "that",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He climbed up a tree ……………………………… to get a good view of the procession.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such as",
                "so as",
                "such that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}